mtishows.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Music Theatre International

These tracking technologies may be deployed by us and/or by our service providers or partners on our behalf. These technologies enable us to assign a unique number to you, and relate your site usage information to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

 **By using the Site, you consent to our use of these tracking technologies as described above.**

 ** _Information Obtained from Third Parties_**

We may supplement the information obtained from you with information that is received or otherwise obtained from third parties. For example, this information may be received or obtained from our partners in sponsored content sections or from other third parties. The type of information that is shared with us could include, for example, user contact information (like name and email address) and user demographic information (like zip code, age or income level), as well as other types of personal information and non-personally identifiable information. We will use such supplemental information received or obtained from third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  

 **Do Not Track Disclosures**

Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" (DNT) signals to the websites with which the user communicates.  Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them.  Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, we currently do not change our tracking practices (which are explained in more detail directly above) in response to DNT settings in your web browser. If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.

Our third party partners, such as ad networks, web analytics companies and social media and networking platforms, collect information about your online activities over time and across our Site and other online properties. These third parties do not change their tracking practices in response to DNT settings in your web browser and we do not obligate these parties to honor DNT settings.  We utilize Google analytics for our web analytics and you can opt out from your data being used by Google Analytics by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. See the discussion above under "Third Party Ad Services and Providers" **** regarding how to opt out of internet-based behavioral advertising.

 **How is your information used?**

We may use personal information of our Users for various purposes, including, for example, to respond to User requests, to administer the Site and your account with us and to provide Users with our product and service offerings, including processing and fulfilling your transactions.  We may also use Users' personal information to maintain our internal record keeping.  We may match information collected from Users through different means or at different times, including both personal information and non-personally identifiable information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including (without limitation) any of our other Web sites and third parties.  We also may use personal information provided by our Users, for the purpose of profiling the demographics of Site users and for developing new features and offerings on the Site. We may use Users' names and email addresses to send notifications regarding the Site, and otherwise correspond with Users, about products, services, companies, events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest our Users.  We also may send announcements, alerts regarding messages received from other Users, and service-related notifications.  If Users want to stop receiving promotional email messages from us, they may do so by following the directions in the ["Opt In/Opt Out"] **** section below.  We may use your personal information enable you to use our Site and its features and to customize our Site to your interests and history with us. We may also use your personal information to protect our rights and property and recover debt and prevent fraud.  In addition, other uses of your information may be disclosed when personal information is submitted to us.

Non-personally identifiable information: We use non-personally identifiable information of and about our Users for various purposes.  For example, cookies may enable us to relate your use of the Web Site to other information about you, including your personal information.   Additionally, we use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to analyze this information to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of the Site, to better tailor the Site to our Users' needs, and to otherwise operate and administer the Site. We may use this information to tailor ads displayed to you on our Site and elsewhere to your interests and history with us. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider.  We may also link this non-personally identifiable information with personal information.

E-mail-A-Friend: Users may be able to send information about our products and/or Site to their friends and family members by using an "E-mail to Friend" or similar feature on the Site or in an e-mail that we have sent them.  In some of these cases (unless a User simply forwards our e-mail on his or her own), the User may provide the name and e-mail address of his or her friend or family member to us.  Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

We or our service providers may also use your information to assess the level of interest in, and use of, the Site, our e-mails and our other messaging campaigns both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. 

 **Do we share your information with third parties?**

Yes.  We may share the information we collect on the Site with others for a variety of reasons.

Service Providers: We may provide information to third party service providers such as server hosts, data management companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies and payment processors (collectively, "Service Providers") in order to facilitate the operation of the Site and its various services and features.  These service providers may be provided or granted access to Users' personal information in order to perform these services on our behalf. 

Legally Required Disclosures: We may comply with judicial requests for Users' personal information, account information, and other information, and make other legally required disclosures. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Site, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

Co-sponsors:  We may share your information with our co-sponsor(s) if we obtain your information in connection with a contest, sweepstakes, offering, or other promotional activity that is jointly offered by us and any third parties, unless you instruct us not to by following the instructions in ["Opt In/Opt Out"

Aggregate Information: Aggregate demographic and other information of and about Users may be published or shared with third parties such as advertisers. In addition, we may share non-personally identifiable Site Usage Information (including aggregate data) with others, for their own use, in a form that does not include your name or contact information.

Third Party Marketers:  We may provide our Users with an opportunity to receive offers from third parties who have services, products and offers that we think might be of interest to them, and we will do so by sharing the User's information with such third parties.  You can elect for us not to do so by following the directions in the ["Opt In/Opt Out"]

Public Forums: When you use the Site, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, other profile information, comments, messages, photos, videos or other content or information, may be shared with other Users of the Site. All such sharing of information and content is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos or other items, this information may become publicly available.  It is important for Users to understand that Users post User Content (as defined in the Site Terms of Use) and information on the Site at their own risk.  We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.

Credit bureaus: We may provide your information to credit bureaus in connection with late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account.

Corporate Change of Control: In the event we, or a significant portion of our assets, are acquired by or transferred to one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, personal information and other User information may be one of the transferred assets.

 **Opt In/Opt Out**

You may have the right to "opt in" and/or "opt out" of certain of our uses of your personal information.  For example, at the time you are requested to provide personal information on this Site or in connection with our communications, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to receive correspondence from us.  You may opt out of our promotional e-mails by clicking on an opt-out or "unsubscribe" link within the promotional e-mail you receive.  Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.  Please also note that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us at your email address, we still may send messages to you (including promotional messages) through the Site's messaging system.

If you want us not to share (or stop sharing) your personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing use, please send us an email at: [websupport@mtishows.com](mailto:websupport@mtishows.com).  If you do request to have us stop sharing your personally information with other entities for their direct marketing purposes, please note that we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your personally identifiable information prior to the date of your request.  In these cases, please contact that entity directly.

 **Social Networking**

We maintain presence on several social networking and blogging platforms, such as Facebook, Twitter, Youtube and Flickr, and we also incorporate some third party social networking features onto our Site.  Through these platforms and features, we receive some personal information and some Site Usage Information about you, and this Privacy Policy applies to that information as well.  In addition, third party social networking platforms and blogging platforms have their own privacy policies which explain how the third parties that provide them will use and protect your information. 

Our Site may include features and functionalities that allow you to share information with us that you have already provided to a third party social networking platform.  For example, you may be able to create an account on our Site or log-in to our Site using your Facebook account or other third party credentials.  If you do so, then personal information or other data that you have provided to that third party will be made available to us, pursuant to the third party's terms and conditions, and you consent to our use of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  The information we receive from that third party may depend on the privacy settings you have on the third party site

We may include tools on our Site that allow you to share and/or publicly post content or information from our Site to your profile on a third party social network.  Third party social networking platforms and blogging platforms have their own privacy policies which explain how they will use, protect and share your information, including any information you share on those platforms from our Site, and we encourage you to read them.

 **Third-Party Ad Servers and Networks**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site or to serve our ads on third-party Web sites.  These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites, the region of the country or world where your IP address indicates you are located, as well as other information about you in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  These advertisements may appear on this Site and on other Web sites.  These companies may employ cookies, clear GIFs and other tracking technologies to cause relevant ads to be displayed to you.  We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies to learn about how they treat your information. 

 **For more information about third-party advertisers and how to prevent them from using your information, visit the NAI's consumer Web site at<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> or Aboutads.info at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.**

 **Links to Third-Party Sites**

The Site may contain links, banners, widgets or advertisements that lead to other Web sites. When you link to such sites, you become subject to their terms of use and privacy policies posted thereon and/or applicable thereto.  We are not responsible in any way for the privacy practices of other web sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided to or collected on any other website. You should review these sites' privacy policies regarding any personal information and other information that they may collect about you at their sites.

 **Security**

While we will endeavor to protect the security and integrity of any sensitive personal information that may be provided to this Site, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. 

If you contact us by e-mail, via a messaging feature, or by a "contact us" or similar feature on the Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure.  A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.  We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

If you create an account on our Site, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any activity that occurs using your account credentials, whether or not you authorized such activity.  Please notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security.

If we believe that the security of any user's personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify such user of that development.  If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail.  You consent to our use of e-mail as the means of such notification.  However, if you do not want to be notified by email for this purpose, please contact us at [websupport@mtishows.com](mailto:websupport@mtishows.com).

 **Accessing, Changing or Removing Information**

You may review, update or modify certain of the information that is stored in your user account on the Site (if you have one) by logging in to the "My Account" or similar area of the Site or by contacting us using the "Contact Us" information below. Users who wish to deactivate their Site account should contact a Site administrator using the contact information at the end of this Privacy Policy. 

We may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information.  Your right to delete your information is subject to our records retention policies.

 **Children**

The Site is intended solely for users who are thirteen (13) years of age or older. We do not knowingly collect personal information from Users under 13 without prior parental consent.  If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide personal information of any kind whatsoever.  If we learn that we have received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will take steps to delete such information or to obtain verifiable parental consent.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and such changes will be effective immediately upon posting.  We will notify you of material changes to this Privacy Policy by other means, including, for example, by posting the revised policy with the date it was revised on this page or by email. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect.

 **Consent to Processing**

By using the Site, you are consenting to have your personal information collected, maintained, transferred and processed in and to the United States and other countries and territories.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about the Site or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [websupport@mtishows.com](mailto:websupport@mtishows.com)

Last Updated: November 20, 2015
